[{"answer": "Consider it done. You are, after all, the people who saved us from the Goa'uld", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What would you like to trade", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. You know that is the one thing we cannot give you. Tollan law strictly forbids it", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The reasons for these laws are still relevant", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It's the thing the that place used to disable our weapons the last time we were there", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Worked on us. And the Goa'uld's", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So, what did you have to promise them in return, Dr my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "They just gave you the device as a reward for saving them from the Goa'uld", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Actually General, we didn't have to promise to give them anything", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Actually General, the my friend refused to give us any technology", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "About", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No Carter. I haven't been acting like myself since I met you. Now I'm acting like myself", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What you've done here is clearly a court martiallable offence. I have to press charges", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I do have one other option I can offer you my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What's the point, if we don't gain anything to help our other interests", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Stuff that interests people like you, my friend. Not people like me. I want to see tangible gains from our efforts. And if people like the that place don't want to share, we should just take", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, in a way, you invited me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "May I come in", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes. What if I told you I could arrange for you to lead a team through the Gate to acquire whatever you want, whenever you want? For the good of this country", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What you did yesterday was very illegal, Colonel", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You've seen my file, my friend. It's only fair I know a little more about you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well I need to know if I'm gonna command this unit", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "And you measure how good you are by the fact that you've never been caught", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sure. I'll take a gander", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend. my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "We do what we can to make it comfortable. I have your first mission, Colonel. Planet PX3 595", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Shades-Of-Grey.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "S", "qsentId": 28}]